[
  {
    "question": "Quel est le résultat de l'expression '2 ** 3 ** 2' en Python, et pourquoi ?",
    "choices": [
      "64, parce que l'exponentiation est évaluée de droite à gauche",
      "512, parce que l'exponentiation est évaluée de gauche à droite",
      "729, parce que l'exponentiation est évaluée de droite à gauche",
      "Aucune des réponses ci-dessus"
    ],
    "answer": "512, parce que l'exponentiation est évaluée de gauche à droite"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the expression '2 ** 3 ** 2' evaluate to in Python, and why?",
    "choices": [
      "64, because exponentiation is evaluated from right to left",
      "512, because exponentiation is evaluated from left to right",
      "729, because exponentiation is evaluated from right to left",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "512, because exponentiation is evaluated from left to right"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result of executing the Python list comprehension '[x**2 for x in range(5) if x%2 == 0]'?",
    "choices": [
      "[0, 1, 4]",
      "[0, 4, 16]",
      "[1, 4, 9]",
      "[0, 2, 4]"
    ],
    "answer": "[0, 4, 16]"
  },
  {
    "question": "1-1 ?",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Big O notation of a binary search algorithm?",
    "choices": [
      "O(log n)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(n log n)",
      "O(n^2)"
    ],
    "answer": "O(log n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which principle focuses on the importance of user-centered design in UX?",
    "choices": [
      "Gestalt Principles",
      "Hick's Law",
      "Fitts's Law",
      "User-Centered Design"
    ],
    "answer": "User-Centered Design"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known as the father of the computer?",
    "choices": [
      "Alan Turing",
      "Charles Babbage",
      "John von Neumann",
      "Ada Lovelace"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Babbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which recent version of Flutter introduced support for foldable devices?",
    "choices": [
      "Flutter 2.0",
      "Flutter 2.5",
      "Flutter 2.8",
      "Flutter 3.0"
    ],
    "answer": "Flutter 2.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary advantage of using Flutter for cross-platform development?",
    "choices": [
      "Access to native device features",
      "Single codebase for multiple platforms",
      "High performance graphics",
      "Large developer community"
    ],
    "answer": "Single codebase for multiple platforms"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first version of Python released?",
    "choices": [
      "1989",
      "1991",
      "2000",
      "2008"
    ],
    "answer": "1991"
  }
]
